Guide to the Dick Thornburgh Papers, 1932- AIS.1998.30.10
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Re-election Campaign for Governor, 1982; X.
  - Campaign in Progress, 7.
    - Endorsements
      - Pecora, Thomas, business manager, Construction General Laborers and Material Handlers Local No. 1058, July 29, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 29)
      - Pennsylvania Builders Association, July, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 30)
      - Pennsylvania Federation of Teachers, September 23, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 31)
      - Pennsylvania Food Merchants, Al Vicks, president, July 2, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 32)
      - Pennsylvania Rifle and Pistol Association, March 30, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 33)
      - Philadelphia Daily News, October 8, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 34)
      - Philadelphia Exclusive, October 29, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 35)
      - Philadelphia Inquirer, October 20, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 36)
      - Philadelphia Times Northeast, October 20, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 37)
      - Philadelphia Tribune, October 22, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 38)
      - Pittsburgh Courier, October 30, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 39)
      - Pittsburgh Post Gazette, October 26, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 40)
      - Pittsburgh Press, October 24, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 41)
      - Pocono Record, October 25, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 42)
      - Polish American Citizens League of Pennsylvania, October 23, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 43)
      - Polish American Congress of Pennsylvania, February 23, 1982; September 20, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 44)
      - Pottstown Mercury, October 26, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 45)
      - Raia, Vic, state commander, American Legion, February 23, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 46)
      - Republican College Council, March 27, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 47)
      - Scranton Scrantonian, October 31, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 48)
      - Scranton Times, October 27, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 49)
      - Scranton Tribune, October 26, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 50)
      - Second Macedonia Baptist Church, September 21, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 51)
      - Seniors for Thornburgh-Scranton Committee, undated (Box 145, Folder 52)
      - Sharon Herald, October 25, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 53)
      - Smith, Jim, columnist, June 25, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 54)
      - Smith, Nate, chairman of the Board, Operation Dig, February 24, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 55)
      - Sportsmen for Thornburgh-Scranton Committee, September, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 56)
      - Stipanovich, Nick, business representative, Pittsburgh Building Trades Council, July 30, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 57)
      - Street, Pennsylvania State Senator, October 22, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 58)
      - Sullivan, Reverend Leon, October 19, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 59)
      - Sunbury Daily Item, October 21, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 60)
      - Tallarico, Joe, president, Mail Handlers Local and Allied Printing Trades Council, July 29, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 61)
      - Teamsters Joint Council No. 40, James Beros, president, October 20, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 62)
      - Teamsters Joint Council No. 53, John Morris, president, April 26, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 63)
      - Teamsters Joint Council No. 341, Ted Zilch, president, and Joe Radan, secretary/treasurer, September 27, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 64)
      - Teamsters Joint Council No. 500, William O'Farrell, president, August 19, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 65)
      - Teamsters 250, Steve Missonak, secretary/treasurer, September 24, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 66)
      - Titusville Herald, October 28, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 67)
      - Transport Workers Union of Philadelphia Local 234, Dominic DiClerico, president, October 5, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 68)
      - Travel and Hospitality Industry Committee for the Reelection of Thornburgh/Scranton, September 21, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 69)
      - Tullio, Louis, Democratic Mayor of Erie, October 21, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 70)
      - Tunkhannock New Age-Examiner, October 29, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 71)
      - Uniontown Herald Standard, October 27, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 72)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, Local Union No. 2274, Frank W. Miller, president, April 2, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 73)
      - United Italian-American Political Alliance, October 22, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 74)
      - Veterans, February 26, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 75)
      - Veterans Political Action Council, April 15, 1982; September 16, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 76)
      - Warren Times-Observer, October 28, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 77)
      - Washington Observer-Reporter, October 26, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 78)
      - WCAU-AM radio, October 18, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 79)
      - WCAU-TV, undated (Box 145, Folder 80)
      - Whitmer, Gil, official, Operating Engineers, July 30, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 81)
      - Wilkes-Barre Times Leader, November 1, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 82)
      - Williams, Carmen J., business manager, Painters Local 327, July 29, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 83)
      - Williamsport Sun Gazette, October 29, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 84)
      - Williamsport Sunday Grit, October 17, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 85)
      - Willow Grove Guide, October 28, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 86)
      - York Daily Record, October 27, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 87)
    - Speeches
      - Governor Thornburgh Announcement Speech, March 2-3, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 88)
      - GOP speech (standard), 1982 (Box 145, Folder 89)
      - Surrogate proposal and plans for speech, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 90)
      - Surrogate speech and background, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 91)
      - Miscellaneous speech to Luzerne County GOP, September 12, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 92)
      - Election Night Remarks, November 2, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 93)
      - Inaugural Address, Harrisburg, PA, January 18, 1983 (Box 145, Folder 94)
    - Questionnaires and Responses
      - Questionnaires and responses: lists, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 95)
      - AAA, August 2, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 96)
      - Allegheny County League of Women Voters, March 31, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 97)
      - American Association of University Women, August 13, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 98)
      - Association for Retarded Citizens, September 8, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 99)
      - Bucks County Council for Exceptional Children, October 7, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 1)
      - Butler County Chapter of Pennsylvanians for Human Life, October 7, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 2)
      - Carnegie Area Concerned Citizens, April 22, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 3)
      - Catholic Conference, September 8, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 4)
      - Common Cause, September, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 5)
      - Commonwealth Association of Students, October 4, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 6)
      - Corry Area Chamber of Commerce, September 30, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 7)
      - Harrisburg Area Women's News, September 17, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 8)
      - League of Women's Voters of Pennsylvania: Primary, March 25, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 9)
      - League of Women's Voters of Pennsylvania: General, August, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 10)
      - Non-public School Action Committee, April 23, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 11)
      - Patriot, October 26, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 12)
      - Penn Lines/Pennsylvania Rural Electric Association, August, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 13)
      - Pennsylvania Farmers' Association, July 9, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 14)
      - Pennsylvania Federation, Council for Exceptional Children, October 6, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 15)
      - Pennsylvania Pharmaceutical Association, September 21, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 16)
      - Pennsylvania Pro-Life Federation, April 8, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 17)
      - Pennsylvania Society for Professional Engineers, Pittsburgh chapter, September 9, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 18)
      - Pennsylvanians for Biblical Morality, April 9, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 19)
      - Pro-Life Coalition, September 8, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 20)
      - Respect for Life, September 8, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 21)
      - United Press International (UPI), May 4, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 22)
      - Valley Forge Council of Republican Women, April 1, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 23)
      - Veterans Political Action Committee: Primary, April 14, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 24)
      - Veterans Political Action Committee: General, August, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 25)
      - Congressional Quarterly, undated (Box 146, Folder 26)
      - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP), possibly not sent, May 7, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 27)
      - Unanswered questionnaires, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 28)
      - Binder of questionnaires and responses, March 25, 1982-August 13, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 29-30)
    - Debate
      - Debate, April-October, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 31)
    - Campaign Controversies and Critics
      - Support groups and letters to editor, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 32)
      - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP), 1982 (Box 146, Folder 33)
      - Pennsylvania State Education Association (PSEA), 1982 (Box 146, Folder 34)
      - Hoffman tape recording, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 35)
      - Ertel income tax disclosure, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 36)
      - Ertel tax break vote, February-June, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 37)
      - Milton Shapp, September-October, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 38)
      - Tony May, August 4, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 39)
      - Governor Thornburgh campaign disclosure, April-September, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 40)
      - Jacobson Gubernatorial challenge, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 41)
      - Bureau of Travel Development newsletter, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 42)
    - Volunteers and Phone Banks
      - Phone bank plans, 1982 (Box 147, Folder 1)
      - Bratas proposal (possibly not used), 1982 (Box 147, Folder 2)
      - Statistics, charts, and forms, 1982 (Box 147, Folder 3)
      - Miscellaneous, 1982 (Box 147, Folder 4)
      - County voter registration tapes, 1982 (Box 147, Folder 5)
      - Western region: phone bank plans, 1982 (Box 147, Folder 6)
      - Western region: Meloy memos, 1982 (Box 147, Folder 7)
      - Western region: Allegheny County business sites, 1982 (Box 147, Folder 8)
    - Ginny Thornburgh Files
      - Campaign Correspondence, 1982 (Box 147, Folder 9)
      - Campaign speech, 1982 (Box 147, Folder 10)
      - General file, 1982 (Box 147, Folder 11)
    - Ephemera
      - Brochures, bumper stickers and buttons, 1982 (Box 147, Folder 12)
    - Volunteer Printout
      - Governor Thornburgh Committee volunteer computer printout, used for Inaugural, 1982-1983 (Box 147, Folder 13)
  - Congratulatory Letters
    - Congratulatory letters VIP's, November 3, 1982-January 14, 1983 (Box 147, Folder 18)
    - ABKR (Alan B.K. Rabinowitz) Christmas Card Memo, November 17, 1982 (Box 147, Folder 19)
    - From Governors, November 3, 1982-January 20, 1983 (Box 147, Folder 20)
    - Foreign, November 4, 1982-January 19, 1983 (Box 147, Folder 21)
    - Out of State, November 1-December 21, 1982 (Box 147, Folder 22)
    - Federally Elected Officials, November 3, 1982-January 17, 1983 (Box 147, Folder 23)
    - Pennsylvania Elected & Appointed Officials, November 3, 1982-January 19, 1983 (Box 147, Folder 24)
    - Judges, November 3, 1982-January 21, 1983 (Box 147, Folder 25)
    - Lawyers, November 3, 1982-January 14, 1983 (Box 147, Folder 26)
    - Local Government, November 3-16, 1982 (Box 147, Folder 27)
    - GOP, October 20-November 22, 1982 (Box 147, Folder 28)
    - Chambers, November 3-8, 1982 (Box 147, Folder 29)
    - Colleges, November 3, 1982-January 25, 1983 (Box 147, Folder 30)
    - Labor, November 3-18, 1982 (Box 147, Folder 31)
    - Veterans, November 3-9, 1982 (Box 147, Folder 32)
    - Media, November 4-23, 1982 (Box 147, Folder 33)
    - Groups, November 3, 1982 (Box 147, Folder 34)
    - Individuals, November 3, 1982-January 18, 1983 (Box 147, Folder 35)
  - Events, 8.
    The Re-election campaign events are separated into two sections: the Thornburgh/Scranton campaign events and the Governor Thornburgh Committee (GTC) campaign events. The Thornburgh/Scranton events cover the primary and general election of 1982. The date range is April 1980-February 1983. The events include press conferences, receptions, interviews, ceremonies, meetings, rallies, and tours.
    The Governor Thornburgh Committee (GTC) events contain attendance lists and background information prior to a meeting with particular associations, organizations, or companies. The events consist of receptions, breakfasts, luncheons, and dinners hosted by the GTC. The files contain information following the time of this re-election campaign, and also regarding the subsequent 1983 Primary election and the 1984 and 1985 General elections. The overall date range is September 1982-November 1985.
    - Thornburgh/Scranton Campaign Events
      - 1980 Primary Election Telephone Calls, Harrisburg, April 22, 1980 (Box 148, Folder 1)
      - 1980 General Election Telephone Calls and Election Day Candidate Information, November 4, 1980 (Box 148, Folder 2)
      - 1981 Primary Election Telephone Calls, Harrisburg, May 18, 1981 (Box 148, Folder 3)
      - 1981 General Election Telephone Calls and Election Day, November 3, 1981 (Box 148, Folder 4)
      - 1982 Primary Election Telephone Calls and Interviews, Harrisburg, March 1, 1982, May 13-18, 1982 (Box 148, Folder 5)
      - 1982 General Election: GOP Candidates Photos and Interviews, Pittsburgh, Harrisburg, Norristown, and Philadelphia, July 15-26, 1982, August 10, 1982, September 1982, November 2, 1982 (Box 148, Folder 6)
      - Thornburgh/Scranton (T/S) Altoona Campaign Headquarters: Ribbon-Cutting Ceremony, Altoona, October 12, 1982 (Box 148, Folder 7)
      - 1982 Press Announcement, Altoona, March 3, 1982 (Box 148, Folder 8)
      - Robert Asher, Republican Chairman, Breakfast, Harrisburg, July 21, 1983 (Box 148, Folder 9)
      - Athletes Endorsement, Pittsburgh, October 14, 1982 (Box 148, Folder 10)
      - 1982 Press Announcement, Erie, March 3, 1982 (Box 148, Folder 11)
      - 1982 Press Announcement, Johnstown, March 3, 1982 (Box 148, Folder 12)
      - 1982 Press Announcement, Philadelphia, March 2, 1982 (Box 148, Folder 13)
      - 1982 Press Announcement, Pittsburgh, March 2, 1982 (Box 148, Folder 14)
      - 1982 Press Announcement at Wilkes-Barre/ Scranton Airport, Avoca, March 3, 1982 (Box 148, Folder 15)
      - Allegheny County Campaigning: GTC Rally and Campaigning at St. Bede's Polling Site, Pittsburgh, October 27, 1982, November 2, 1982 (Box 148, Folder 16)
      - Building and Construction Trades: Meeting, Pittsburgh, June 16, 1982 (Box 148, Folder 17)
      - Business Leaders: Luncheon, Harrisburg, June 28, 1982 (Box 148, Folder 18)
      - Butler County Headquarters: Visit, Butler, October 27, 1982 (Box 148, Folder 19)
      - Clearfield County Headquarters: Ribbon-Cutting Ceremony, Clearfield, September 10, 1982 (Box 148, Folder 20)
      - Democrats for Thornburgh/Scranton: Press Announcements, Pittsburgh and Philadelphia, September 22, 1982 (Box 148, Folder 21)
      - Educators: Visit and Breakfast, Harrisburg, May 23, 1982, May 24, 1982 (Box 148, Folder 22)
      - Erie County Headquarters: Ribbon-Cutting, Erie, October 21, 1982 (Box 148, Folder 23)
      - Fraternal Order of Police Endorsement: Press Announcement, Philadelphia, September 23, 1982 (Box 148, Folder 24)
      - Farmers Endorsement, Press Availability and Luncheon Tribute to Dick Thornburgh, Elizabethtown and Harrisburg, July 8, 1982, October 8, 1982 (Box 148, Folder 25)
      - Firefighters Endorsement, Press Conference, and Luncheon, Carlisle, September 11, 1982 (Box 148, Folder 26)
      - "Join the Champs" Party: Reception and Rally, McKeesport, August 10, 1982 (Box 148, Folder 27)
      - Labor Leaders Endorsement, Luncheon, Meeting, and Press Announcement, Philadelphia and Pittsburgh, February 25, 1982, June 16, 1982, July 29, 1982 (Box 148, Folder 28)
      - Labor Rally: Italian Market Tour and Dinner, Philadelphia, April 22, 1982, October 19, 1982, October 30,1982 (Box 148, Folder 29)
      - Lancaster County Rally and Tour, Lancaster, October 29, 1982 (Box 148, Folder 30)
      - Lawrence County Headquarters: Visit, New Castle, October 28, 1982 (Box 148, Folder 31)
      - Lehigh Valley Rally, Allentown, October 29, 1982 (Box 148, Folder 32)
      - John Morris, President of Teamsters: Meeting, Harrisburg, January 13, 1982 (Box 148, Folder 33)
      - Henry Nicholas Endorsement, Philadelphia, October 15, 1982 (Box 148, Folder 34)
      - Northampton County Rally, Easton, October 29, 1982 (Box 148, Folder 35)
      - Northeast Rally and Press Conference, Avoca, November 1, 1982 (Box 148, Folder 36)
      - PA Dental Association: Meeting, Harrisburg, June 8, 1982 (Box 148, Folder 37)
      - PA Farmers Union Board of Directors: Meeting, Harrisburg, July 23, 1982 (Box 148, Folder 38)
      - PA Federation of Teachers Endorsement and Press Availability, September 6, 1982, September 23, 1982 (Box 148, Folder 39)
      - Perry County: Buffet and Rally, New Bloomfield, September 2, 1982 (Box 148, Folder 40)
      - Polish-American Citizens League Endorsement, Harrisburg, September 20, 1982 (Box 148, Folder 41)
      - Polish Rally, Philadelphia, October 28, 1982 (Box 148, Folder 42)
      - Republican State Committee Endorsement: Reception and Meeting, Harrisburg, March 12, 1982, March 13, 1982 (Box 148, Folder 43)
      - Small Business Endorsement and Tour, McKees Rocks, September 30, 1982 (Box 148, Folder 44)
      - Teamsters Endorsement and Meeting with John Morris, President, Pittsburgh and Philadelphia, October 20, 1982, June 17, 1982 (Box 148, Folder 45)
      - Transport Workers Union Endorsement, Philadelphia, October 6, 1982 (Box 148, Folder 46)
      - Travel Endorsement, Harrisburg, September 21, 1982 (Box 148, Folder 47)
      - Lou Tullio Endorsement, Erie, October 21, 1982 (Box 148, Folder 48)
      - United Transportation Union: Luncheon, Seven Springs, August 6, 1982 (Box 148, Folder 49)
      - Veterans: Meeting, Harrisburg, February 26, 1982 (Box 148, Folder 50)
      - York County Rally, York, October 31, 1982 (Box 148, Folder 51)
      - 1983 Inaugural information, Harrisburg, January 18, 1983 (Box 148, Folder 52)
      - 1983 Inaugural Committee Reception, Harrisburg, February 24, 1983 (Box 148, Folder 53)
    - Governor Thornburgh Committee (GTC) Campaign Events
      - Asian-Pacific Association: Reception and Dinner, Philadelphia, September 11, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 1)
      - Bachelors Barge Club: Dinner, Philadelphia, March 31, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 2)
      - Herb Barness, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 3)
      - Bear, Stearns, and Company: Breakfast, New York, NY, May 25, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 4)
      - Remo Butera Luncheons, Philadelphia, June 18, 1982, September 23, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 5)
      - Peter Carlino Reception, Blue Bell, June 17, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 6)
      - Centre County Reception, State College, March 22, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 7)
      - Clarion County, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 8)
      - Dairy Farm Filming, Mechanicsburg, September 30, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 9)
      - Craig Dare Reception, Horsham, May 16, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 10)
      - Dauphin County and Republican Committee Breakfast and Visit, Harrisburg, September 25, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 11)
      - Erie County Reception, Erie, August 11, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 12)
      - Sam Evans and Family of Leaders Rally, Philadelphia, October 26, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 13)
      - Filming Thank You Notes, August 30, 1982, October 18, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 14)
      - Gerald Ford: Western Kick-off Dinner with Gerald Ford, Pittsburgh, March 22, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 15)
      - Richard Fox: Dinner, Penn Valley, June 17, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 16)
      - Chris Gleason: Luncheon, Johnstown, July 17, 1981 (Box 149, Folder 17)
      - Dr. Joseph Haller: Reception, Hollidaysburg, October 12, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 18)
      - Hershey Dinner, Hershey, March 2, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 19)
      - Ober Hess: Brunch, Gladwyne, September 19, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 20)
      - Hispanic Community: Reception, Philadelphia, June 29, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 21)
      - Harold Horn: Reception, Paradise, June 25, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 22)
      - Indiana County: Reception and Dinner, Indiana, August 5, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 23)
      - Insurance Federation of PA: Breakfast and Remarks, Philadelphia, April 1, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 24)
      - Jefferson County: Reception and Dinner, Punxsutawney, September 10, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 25)
      - Juniata County: Breakfast, Mifflintown, September 2, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 26)
      - John Kaufman: Reception, Ambler, September 19, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 27)
      - Bruce Kauffman: Reception, Gladwyne, April 18, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 28)
      - Charles Kirkwood-Northeast: Fundraiser, Shawnee-On-Delaware, July 22, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 29)
      - Henry Kissinger: Reception and Dinner, Philadelphia, September 23, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 30)
      - Malcolm Lazin: Dinner and VIP Reception, Philadelphia, March 18, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 31)
      - Lehigh and Northampton Counties: Reception and Dinner, Allentown, June 12, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 32)
      - Charles Lockhart: Reception, Washington, D.C., June 24, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 33)
      - Lycoming County: Reception, Williamsport, September 27, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 34)
      - Mario Mele: Meeting and Luncheons, Philadelphia, January 21, 1982, March 18, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 35)
      - Nathan Mao: VIP Reception and Dinner, Chambersburg, May 27, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 36)
      - Sam McCullough and Joe Welch: Buffet Reception, Wyomissing, May 28, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 37)
      - Northeastern PA: Dinner, Old Forge, September 14, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 38)
      - Northwest Regional Campaign Committee: Reception and Dinner, Warren, September 9, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 39)
      - John O'Hara: Reception, Ardmore, April 18, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 40)
      - PA Food Merchants Association: Meeting, Harrisburg, October 14, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 41)
      - PA Medical Society: Reception, Harrisburg, July 26, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 42)
      - Philadelphia Club: Luncheon, Philadelphia, October 1, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 43)
      - Mrs. Vivian Piasecki and Mrs. Ann P. Curran: Luncheon, Villanova, February 1, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 44)
      - Pittsburgh: Reception and Dinner, Pittsburgh, September 30, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 45)
      - Radio Spots: Radio Commercial Taping, Harrisburg, October 7, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 46)
      - Ronald Reagan: Luncheon, Philadelphia, May 14, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 47)
      - Don Rose and Ernie Buckman: Breakfast, Sewickley, June 26, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 48)
      - Evans Rose: Fundraising Reception, Pittsburgh, May 23, 1984 (Box 149, Folder 49)
      - Ken Ross and Ed Lewis: Luncheon, Pittsburgh, May 6, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 50)
      - Ralph Scalera: Reception and Buffet, Beaver, July 29, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 51)
      - Schuylkill County: Reception, Ashland, August 13, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 52)
      - Richard Schweiker: Press Availability, Reception, and Dinner, Hershey, October 18, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 53)
      - W.W. Scranton, II: Reception, Scranton, September 14, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 54)
      - Seminar and Luncheon, Harrisburg, April 24, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 55)
      - David Shakarian: Luncheon, Harrisburg, September 20, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 56)
      - Susquehanna Valley: Luncheon, Shamokin Dam, September 2, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 57)
      - Joseph Walker, Jr.: Receptions and Luncheon, New York, NY, May 6, 1982, May 25, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 58)
      - Harold Yoh: Reception, Bryn Mawr, May 16, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 59)
      - 1982 General Election Night Festivities, Philadelphia, November 2, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 60)
      - Victory Gala: Reception and Dinner, Harrisburg, December 14, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 61)
      - Ginny Thornburgh Campaign Staff Dinner, Harrisburg, November 12, 1982 (Box 149, Folder 62)
      - 1983 Primary Election Telephone Calls, Harrisburg, May 16, 1983 (Box 149, Folder 63)